lagbook.com 2013-12-15

# Privacy | PicRate

PicRate takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. Also note that your use of PicRate, along with disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our TOS. PicRate shall comply with all applicable laws.

### What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how PicRate treats information that PicRate collects and receives, including information related to your past use of PicRate products and services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that PicRate does not own or control (including, but not limited to, advertisers), or to people that PicRate does not employ or pay.

### Information Collection and Use

PicRate collects information when you register with PicRate, when you use PicRate products or services, and when you visit PicRate pages or the pages of certain PicRate affiliates, vendors, or advertisers. PicRate may collect information about you and your use of PicRate that is both personal and non-personal. For purposes of this policy, “personal information” is information about you that can be used to personally identify you, such as your email address, and that is not otherwise publicly available. “Non-personal” information is everything else.

When you register to use PicRate we ask for information such as your email address, birth date, gender, etc. Once you register with PicRate and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

PicRate may also collect information about your transactions with us and your transactions with our business affiliates, vendors, and advertisers, including information about your use of products offered through PicRate. PicRate may also collect information about you from other sources, such as blogs and instant messaging services, and other users of PicRate services. PicRate automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, PicRate cookie information (including without limitation cookies, flash cookies, and beacons), and the pages you request.

When you use or connect to the PicRate website or download a PicRate mobile app by or through a Third Party Platform, such as Facebook or another social networking site, we may also access and/or collect certain information from your Third Party Platform profile/account (such as your Facebook account) or via any cookies placed on your device by such Third Party Platform as permitted by the terms of the agreement and your privacy settings with the Third Party Platform. We will share such information with the Third Party Platform for their use as permitted by the terms of the agreement and your privacy setting with the Third Party Platform.

PicRate may use some or all of your information for the following general purposes:

  * To customize your experience
  * To customize advertising and content you see
  * To fulfill your requests for products and services
  * To offer customized features
  * To improve our services
  * To contact you
  * To conduct research and/or data analytics

These activities, in part, help to underwrite the cost of the content and services made available to you online. Note that, in general, tracking of a user’s online activities over time — including the searches conducted, the web pages visited, and the content viewed — in order to deliver targeted advertising is considered online behavioral advertising. NOTE THAT PICRATE USERS ARE SUBJECT TO ONLINE BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING AND/OR MULTI-SITE ADVERTISING.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

PicRate may share with or sell to affiliates, vendors, service providers, advertisers, and other non-related third parties your non-personal information for commercial purposes. PicRate may also share with affiliates, vendors, advertisers, and other non-related third parties your non-personal information in order to allow PicRate and its affiliates, vendors, advertisers and other non-related third parties to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience. However, PicRate does not sell, rent or otherwise provide your personal information, including your email address, to any third parties without your permission, other than as specified below:

  * PicRate may share your personal and/or non-personal information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes, or, when necessary, to establish or exercise PicRate’s legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * PicRate may share your personal and/or non-personal information with appropriate authorities when PicRate, in its sole discretion, believes that it is necessary to share such information in order to facilitate an investigation, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or in similar situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations or suspected violations of PicRate’s TOS related to personal safety, or as otherwise required by law.

Notwithstanding any of the aforementioned, be aware that posting personal information on public areas of PicRate (via Profile, Forums, Blogs, etc.) will make your information publicly available. Do not post information in public areas that you want to keep private. Also, be aware that certain information you post or share with third parties like your friends or members of your network about yourself may be shared with other users and all such sharing of information is done at your own risk.

Mobile Users: We collect personal user data including mobile device identification (UDID, device ID, etc.) and geographic location, and upload it to our servers. It is used to track usage, prevent spam, and enhance functionality, and it is passed to third-party vendors to compile analytics and target advertising.

### Communication from PicRate

PicRate may contact you via email with service related notifications and announcements. With the exception of essential account related emails, you may opt out of all email communication from PicRate on your notification settings page. Non-members may block all email communication from PicRate by emailing [info@picrate.me](mailto:info@picrate.me) with the subject “Unsubscribe.”

### Links

PicRate is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites that may be linked to PicRate pages. You are solely responsible for reviewing third party privacy policy terms. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by PicRate.

### Inviting Friends

When you search for friends or invite friends on PicRate, you will be asked to provide your friends’ names, email addresses, and/or mobile phone numbers. By clicking a button/link like “find friends,” “add friends,” “add + invite friends,” “add + email friends” or such other button and/or link text that may signal your intent, you give PicRate permission to import your address book contacts including email addresses and phone numbers and store their names and email addresses indefinitely. We will use this information to send people you select a message and/or SMS text message on your behalf using your name, photo, email address and/or mobile phone number. We may also send a limited number of reminders to them in your name. We may also use this information to suggest friends to PicRate members, including to you. Your information will be stored in a safe and secure manner. We will make no other use of this information for any other marketing purpose without notification.

### Cookies

PicRate may set and access PicRate  cookies on your computer to, among other things, customize the user experience. These files help more precisely target advertising to you based on your activity, but such files do not access or use information by which you can be personally identified. You may realize certain losses of functionality if you turn your cookies off in your browser, or otherwise disable them.

Affiliates, vendors, advertisers, and other non-related third parties displayed on PicRate may also contain cookies or tag your computer with cookies. PicRate does not control these third party cookies and, for your own benefit, you should check the privacy policy of such third parties. Third party ads displayed on PicRate may also include tags enabling such third parties to collect information about the user’s interaction with such ads. For instance, by way of illustration and not limitation, such third party tags may record the date, time, user’s geographical location based on the user’s IP address, as well as the website to which the ad was delivered, the operating system which the browser was using, and so on. Note that if you choose to block some or all cookies you may not have access to certain PicRate features and you may adversely affect your experience of PicRate.

For more information about cookies, web beacons, and related tools that may be used by PicRate and non-related third parties, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>.

### Opting Out of Receiving Cookies

Some of PicRate’s vendors and affiliates are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) and as members they comply with NAI’s Self-Regulatory Principles which are designed to inform consumers about data collection and advertising practices across multiple web sites and provide the ability to users to opt out.

YOU MAY OPT OUT OF RECEIVING COOKIES BY CLICKING HERE: [HTTP://NETWORKADVERTISING.ORG/MANAGING/OPT_OUT.ASP](http://networkadvertising.org/MANAGING/OPT_OUT.ASP)

Note that if you use multiple computers or multiple browsers, you will need to opt out of receiving cookies on each computer and for each browser. Also, if you change computers or delete cookies from your computer you will need to repeat this opt-out process.

You may “opt out” of the collection of your information for third party analytics purposes by our vendor HasOffers by following the directions provided by our third party analytics vendor located at <http://www.mobileapptracking.com/privacy-policy/>. If you “opt out” with this third party analytics provider, that action is specific to the information we collect specifically for that provider, and does not limit our ability to collect information from you, under the terms of this privacy policy, for other vendors.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

PicRate reserves the right to update and change this Privacy Policy and/or its TOS at any time. All updates and changes to this Privacy Policy and/or its TOS shall take effect immediately. Although PicRate shall announce significant changes by posting a notice prominently on PicRate for your convenience, you assume the responsibility of periodically reviewing this Privacy Policy and PicRate encourages you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand the current Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, the most current Privacy Policy applies.

**Contact Information:**  
Bazaar Media Pte. Ltd.  
#07-10/11  
51 Goldhill Plaza  
Singapore, 308900  

Last Updated: March 20, 2013
